Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- NY Telephone Co. - Customer Literature, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Topics for Telephone People, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
    By New York Telephone Co. December 1953 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Practical Relations in Business, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
    By Keith S. McHugh. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Long Range Business Policies: A Case Study, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Why We Keep the Public Informed, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
    By New York Telephone Co. September 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Why We Keep the Public Informed, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
    By New York Telephone Co. September 1952 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Why We Keep the Public Informed, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
    By New York Telephone Co. September 1952 - Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Olin Industries - Rise of House of Olin, Publication (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Rise of the House of Olin, Publication (Box 38, Folder 22)
    By Richard Austin Smith. December 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Rise of the House of Olin, Publication (Box 38, Folder 22)
    By Richard Austin Smith. December 1953 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Rise of the House of Olin, Publication (Box 38, Folder 22)
    By Richard Austin Smith. December 1953 - Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Porter Cable - Advertising Material, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Bench Grinder - Model BBS, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. July 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Porter-Cable Wet Belt Surfacer, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Porter-Cable Wet and Dry Belt Surfacer, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Dec. 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Abrasive Belt Grinder, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Porter-Cable B-3 10'' Dry Belt Surfacer Used Horizontally or Vertically, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Porter-Cable B-6W and B-6D Wet and Dry Flexible Belt Surfaces, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Porter-Cable C-6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Bulletin No. 660. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Porter-Cable Wet-or-Dry Belt Centerless Grinder Type L-4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Save Money on Every Floor Sanding Job with a Speedmatic, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: New 12-inch Drum Speedmatic Speedliner Floor Sander, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Year after Year you can Make more Money with the Guild R-8 Rental Floor Sander, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Form No. 652. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Porter-Cable Floor Edgers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Form no. 669. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Welcome to Porter-Cable, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: Finishing Sander Model 105, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 15: Portable Belt Sander, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Form No. 779. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bench Grinders by Porter-Cable, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 17: Porter-Cable Guild Tools, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
    By Porter-Cable Machine Company. Form No. 772. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: New Porter-Cable Backstand Idlers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 19: Porter Cable Speedmatic; Router, Shaper, Mortiser, Plane and Accessories, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Item 20: Porter-Cable Speedmatic Tools; Electric Hand Saws and Electric Belt Sanders, Publication (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Prudential Insurance Company of America, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Prudential Insurance Company of America and Insurance Agents' International Union, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
    By Prudential Insurance Company of America. March 15, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Digest, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
    By Prudential Insurance Company of America. March 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Security for you and your family, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: POG Service Awards, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: First Class Mail, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Field Management Digest, Publication (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Raymond Corporation - Job Descriptions, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By The Raymond Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1957 Annual Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By The Raymond Corporation. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: You and The Raymond Corporation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: You and The Raymond Coporation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Oganization Chart, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Production Department Organization Chart, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Reporter, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By The Raymond Corporation. June 1, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report on the Road Issue, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By Harry C. Triandia. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Marketing Division: Five Year Forecast, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: 1958 Budget Worksheets, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Employee Appraisal Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Employee Appraisal Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Employee Appraisal Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By The Raymond Corporation. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Employee Appraisal Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 25)
    By The Raymond Corporation. Copy 4. Item is in English.
- Raymond Corporation - Management Guides, Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Publication (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Raymond Corporation - Sales, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Raymond Management Guide, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Raymond Management Guide: 16.1 Work Areas, Publication (Box 38, Folder 27)
    By The Raymond Corporation. March 31, 1958. Item is in English.
- Raymond Corporation - Training Program, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Terriotory Comparative Report of Unit Sales, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: The Raymond Corporation - Agency Survey Report, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Monthly Checklist, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Service on Electric Trucks, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Service on Hit & Lap Trucks, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Service on L2P Hand Trucks, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: The Industrial Truck Association, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: A totally new concept in Walkies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: 4 -D Narrow aisle Electric Truck, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Memorized Hand Truck Reports receive for May 1955, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Gasoline Truck reports received for May 1955, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: Gasoline Powered Tractor reports received for May 1955, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Association of Lift Truck and Portable Elevator Manufacturers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: Association of Lift Truck and Portable Elevator Manufacturers, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Industrial Truck Catalog, Publication (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Sears, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Product School, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Service School, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Memorandum: Training Program - Carleton Everett, Publication (Box 38, Folder 29)
    By The Raymond Corporation. November 1, 1956. Item is in English.
- Seneca Ordnance Depot, Romulus, New York, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Sears National Personnel Department, Publication (Box 38, Folder 30)
    By Sears. Item is in English.
- SHELL - Program for Security, Publication (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Problems in Management for Top Executives, Publication (Box 38, Folder 31)
    By Seneca Ordnance Department. may 1955. Item is in English.
- SOHIO - Employee Literature, Publication (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Program for Security, Publication (Box 38, Folder 32)
    By SHELL. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Program for Security, Publication (Box 38, Folder 32)
    By SHELL. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- SOHIO - Employment Forms, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Employees' Mutual Benefit Corporation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
    By SOHIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: About You and Sohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: About You and Sohio, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
    By SOHIO. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Summary of Sohio Benefit Plans and Policies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Summary of Sohio Benefit Plans and Policies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: SOHIO Employees Investment Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: SOHIO Employees Investment Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: General Safety Rules and Instructions \, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
    By SOHIO. March 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: General Safety Rules and Instructions, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: SOHIO Scholarship Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Item 11: SOHIO Scholarship Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 33)
- SOHIO - Union Agreement, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Performance Report for Technical Personnel, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Bayway Refinery, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Application for Payment, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Performance Report for Non-Supervisory Office Personnel, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Performance Report for Non-Supervisory Office Personnel, Publication (Box 38, Folder 34)
- SOHIO - Organization Charts, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Agreement between The Standarf Oil CO. and Refinery Workers' Federal Labor Union, Publication (Box 38, Folder 35)
    By SOHIO. February 27, 1951. Item is in English.
- SOHIO - Supervisor's Manual No. 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Southern Airways, Publication (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual No. 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 37)
- SRA Employment Inventory Information Kit, Publication (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Airroute Map, Publication (Box 38, Folder 38)
    By Southern Airways. Item is in English.
- Standard Oil (New Jersey) - Employee Lit., Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Survey Analyzer, Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
    By SRA Employee Inventory. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Information Kit, Publication (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Todd Company, Rochester New York, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: May We Quote You?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
    By Standard Oil New Jersey. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: May We Quote You?, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
    By Standard Oil New Jersey. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: It has happened here!, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: It has happened here!, Publication (Box 38, Folder 40)
- United Fruit Company: Employee Literature, Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Todd News Topics, Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
    By Todd Company. Vol.14, No.7, July-August 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Todd News Topics, Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
    By Todd Company. Vol.14, No.5, June 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Todd News Topics, Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
    By Todd Company. Vol.14, No. 9, October-November 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Policies and Standard Practices of the Todd Company, Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
    By Todd Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 38, Folder 41)
- U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
    By U.S. Atomic Energy Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Illustrative List of Branch Projects, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
    By U.S. Atomic Energy Commission. may 1, 1958. Item is in English.
- U.S.A.F., Wright-Patterson Base, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: HQ AMC Orgnizational Objectives and Concept of Staff Operation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By U.S.A.F. Wright-Patterson Base. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Diseases of the organization, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Diseases of the Organization, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By U.S.A.F. Wright-Patterson Base. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Diseases of the Organization, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By U.S.A.F. Wright-Patterson Base. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: HQ AMC Organizational Objectives and Concept of Staff Operation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: HQ AMC Organizational Objectives and Concept of Staff Operation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: HQ AMC Organizational Objectives and Concept of Staff Operation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By U.S.A.F. Wright-Patterson Base. Copy 4. Item is in English.
- U.S.A.F. - Handout Material, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 12, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    By U.S.A.F. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 12, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 12, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 12, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 13, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 13, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 14, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 14, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Instructor's Outline for Lesson 14, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
- U.S.A.F., Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Memorandums and Notes, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
- U.S. Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By U.S. Steel Corporation. Item is in English.
- Panel Manual -- Jan. 26, 2010, Publication (Box 40)